A mirror inside the wedding cake?
مرآة داخل كعكة الزواج؟
Yeah! If you can put a mirror inside of it,
أجل، إذا استطعت وضع مرآة داخل الكعكة
we can bust out, straight from mirror dimension!
سأتمكن من الخروج من بُعد المرآة بطريقة مدهشة
It'll be be fun and sweet!
حينها سيكون الأمر ممتعًا ولذيذًا
You're not here to have fun!
لا حاجة للذة والمتعة
Don't make me repeat myself! Your job is...
...لا تجعلني أكرر كلامي، مهمتك هي
I know! You want me to break the picture, right?
أعلم، تريد مني تحطيم الصورة، صحيح؟
But it won't hurt to have fun while doing it!
لهذا السبب أريد الخروج بطريقة ممتعة حينما أفعل ذلك
Don't be ridiculous!
لا تكن سخيفًا
You want to destroy the wedding cake?
هل تفكر بإفساد كعكة الزواج؟
You have no idea how much Mama's been looking forward to it...
...أنتم لا تدركون حجم ترقّب ماما لها
You made the copies of Nami and the others in the woods, right?
لقد قمتِ بصناعة نُسخ من نامي والبقية في الغابة، صحيح؟
Yeah!
أجل
She can make copies of a person
يمكن لبروليه صنع نسخة عن شخص من خلال عكس صورته على المرآة وتعريضها لحيوان آخر
So what?!
ماذا ستفعل إذًا؟
I caught them... Make them look like me.
أمسكت بهم، قومي بتحويلهم إلى نسخ مني
Father!
الأب
Oh, you all done?
هل انتهيتم؟
Everything is ready-rero.
التجهيزات مكتملة-ريرو
Okay. Good job.
أحسنتم عملًا
It's on now...
ها قد بدأت
P-People are coming out of the cake!
ثـ-ثمة أشخاص يخرجون من الكعكة
Oh my! I can't believe it!
مذهل، مذهل
Another flashy show...
إنه عرض مبهرج آخر
No, that's not it, Du Feld. This is big news!
مخطئ يا دو فلد، إنها أنباء صادمة
He's a pirate from the Worst Generation!
إنه قرصان من الجيل الأسوأ
Straw Hat Luffy!
قبعة القش لوفي
The unimaginable is happening!
أمر غير متوقع حدوثه البتة
Why is he here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
Are they all Straw Hat?
هل جمعيهم قبعة القش؟
Why are there so many of him?
لِمَ هناك الكثير؟
Run! The cake is collapsing!
اهربوا، الكعكة تنهار
What are they?!
ما خطبهم؟
Straw Hat Luffy?!
قبعة القش لوفي؟
That bastard!
ذلك الوغد
Pudding-chan, calm down!
تماسكي يا بودينغ-تشان
It's finally started... This is all going to be decided in an instant.
بدأت الخطة أخيرًا، اللحظة الحاسمة ستحدث في أي لحظة
You can do it, Luffy!
أعتمد عليك يا لوفي
What's going on, Mont d'Or?!
ما الخطب يا مونت دور؟
I thought Straw Hat Luffy and the girl died in the Prisoner Library!
ظننتُ أنّ قبعة القش لوفي وتلك الفتاة قد هلكا في سجن المكتبة
Dammit!
سحقًا
Opera, that dumbass... He really was lying!
كنتُ واثقًا أنّ الوغد أوبرا يكذب
He was trying to cover his own ass!
أنّى له أن يكذب لينفذ بجلده؟
My...
...كعكتي
precious...
...العزيزة
cake is...
...الكعكة
The cake is...
...إنّ الكعكة
What the...?!
ما الأمر؟
She's acting weird...
إنها تتصرف بغرابة
No... I was looking forward to that...
كلا، كنت أتحرق شوقًا لها
Mama, please keep your composure! I know how you're feeling.
ماما، حافظي على رباطة جأشك، أتفهم شعورك جيدًا
Cake!
الكعكة
Head Chef! Run for it!
ابتعد عن المكان يا رئيس الطهاة
Mama's acting strange!
ماما تتصرف بغرابة
Bring me a new cake...!
أعد لي كعكة جديدة
Th-That's impossible...
هـ-هذا مستحيل
Life...
...الحياة
or...
...أو
wedding cake?!
كعكة الزفاف؟
G-Guys...
يا رفاق
It's her Soul Pocus!
إنّها قدرة كلمات الروح
She's going to take their lifespans! What a scoop!
سيتم سلب حياتهم، إنه نبأ مثير
Big Mom can speak directly to the human soul's fixation on its own life!
بيغ مام قادرة على الاستفادة من تشبث المرء بحياته
If a person fears death at all, they'll be vulnerable to it...
...إن كان يخشى الموت ولو قليلًا
Look! That's it!
انظر، أرواحهم تخرج
H... H-Help!
ا-النجدة
No!
كلا
If you don't give me what I want,
كل من يفسد ملذاتي وسعادتي
I'll take your lifespan to make up for it!
سأسلبه حياته
Go! Go!
هيا، هيا
Okay, that way!
استمروا على هذا المنوال
That voice... It sounds like Big Mom's throwing a fit out there!
الصوت الذي سمعناه للتو يعكس مدى اشتياط بيغ مام غضبًا
We're pretty desperate in here too!
القلق أحاط بنا نحن أيضًا
The situation is messier than we expected it to be!
الفوضى ازدادت أكثر مما توقعنا
I'll make you pay for this!
سأجعلك تدفع ثمن هذا
Is that all of them?
هل أطلقتم سراحهم جميعًا؟
This Luffy is the last!
هذه هي النسخة الأخيرة من لوفي
All right! Let's go, Pedro!
عظيم، لنذهب يا بيدرو
Yeah! Let's give Luffy some backup!
أجل، لدعم لوفي
We're going too! To back up Sanji-kun !
يجب أن نذهب أيضًا لدعم سانجي-كن
Are you ready?
هل أنتِ جاهزة؟
Yeah! I've got my earplugs!
أجل، بحوزتي سدادات الأذن
We'll rescue Sanji's family!
سننقذ عائلة سانجي
Okay, we'll leave the rest to you, human scum.
والآن سنترك الباقي عليك أيها الحثالة
Is he really that bad?
هل هو بهذا السوء؟
He's the worst!
إنه الأسوأ
Once I get my heart back, I'll teach them a lesson...
سأجعلكم تدفعون الثمن غاليًا حالما أستعيد قلبي
That bastard, Straw Hat...
قبعة القش الوغد
How dare he mess with me!
لا تعبث معي
You bastard!
أيها اللعين
Which one is the real Straw Hat?!
أيهم قبعة القش؟
Monkey D. Luffy...
مونكي دي لوفي
I'll remember that name.
سأتذكر اسمك
Come! To the New World!
تعال إلى العالم الجديد
What a stupid story...
يا لها من قصة مملة
You're the one who hasn't become
أنتِ التي فشلتِ في أن تصبحي ملكة القراصنة
I'm here to pick another fight with you!
سأفتعل قتالًا معكِ مجددًا
Don't be cocky just because you're an emperor!
إياكِ وأن يأخذ بكِ الكبر لمجرد أنكِ إمبراطورة
I'm going to take Sanji back!
سأستعيد سانجي حتمًا
And in the end, we're the ones who'll win!
ونحن من سيظفر بالنصر
The cake has... collapsed...
الكعكة... قد تحطمت
Dammit...
سحقًا
How dare he ruin my wedding cake!
كيف يجرؤ على إفساد كعكة الزفاف؟
Which one's the real Straw Hat Luffy?!
أيهم قبعة القش الحقيقي؟
Where is he?!
أين هو؟
What an idiot. This is just a diversion.
أهي حمقاء؟ إنها خطة تشتيت
Show yourself! Straw Hat!
أظهر نفسك يا قبعة القش
Does she really expect him to reveal himself?
أتظنه سيرد عليها؟
I mean, if he responds...
...لن يقوم بالرد
It's me!
أنا هنا
He... He responded!
لـ-لقد ردّ عليها
There you are, Straw Hat...
ها أنت ذا يا قبعة القش
I'll crush you!
سأمزقك إربًا إربا
There's the picture frame!
ها هو إطار الصورة
Vito... Gotti... Are the launchers ready?
فيتو، غوتي، هل قاذفة الصواريخ جاهزة؟
Yes, we can jump out anytime, Father.
أجل، بإمكاننا الخروج متى شئت أيها الأب
Straw Hat... Do your best.
قبعة القش، افعل ما في وسعك
No, let go of me!
كلا، دعني
The flock keeps coming!
مجموعة منهم قادمة
Come on!
تقدّم
That must be the real Luffy.
ذلك لوفي الحقيقي بلا شك
Once Luffy breaks the picture, we'll burst in after three seconds...
سننطلق بعد ثلاث ثواني من تحطيم لوفي للصورة
Uh-huh...
أجل
Are you listening? Be serious!
هل تستمعان لي؟ لا يمكنكما التصرف بطيش هكذا
Zeus!
زيوس
Yes, Mama!
حاضر يا ماما
Prometheus!
بروميثيوس
I'll take them all out at once!
سأقضي عليهم جميعًا بضربة واحدة
Okay!
عظيم
This'll be easy!
مهمة سهلة
Take this!
إليك هذه
He can do it!
يمكنه فعلها
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
This is the real one!
هذا هو الحقيقي
The other versions of Straw Hat are
...بقية نُسخ قبعة القش
just animals from the island that were transformed by Brûlée's ability.
ما هم إلا حيوانات الجزيرة تمّ تحويلهم بواسطة قدرة بروليه
Ignore them!
لا تلقي لهم بالًا
I see! So they used Brûlée's ability!
فهمت، إذًا هم استخدموا قدرة بروليه
Damn...
سحقًا
What the hell is this?!
ما هذا يا تُرى؟
My limbs are buried and I can't pull them out! What kind of ability is this?!
لا يمكنني سحب أطرافي، ما هذه القدرة؟
Katakuri! You think I need help?
كاتاكوري، هل تحاول مساعدتي؟
You're my son; I don't need...
...أنت ابني، ولا يمكنك
No, Mama!
كلا يا ماما
He was targeting...
...كان هدفه
Mother Carmel's portrait.
صورة الأم كارمل
How do you know its importance to us?
أنّى لك معرفة أنها مهمة؟
I thought only our allies knew.
وحدهم الأشخاص المقربين يعرفون ذلك
Spit it out! Who told you?
تحدث، من أخبرك؟
Shut up! Let go of me, you idiot!
اخرس، دعني أيها الوغد
Damn... The plan's in ruins.
سحقًا، لقد تمّ عرقلة الخطة
Somebody! Just break the picture!
ليحطم أحدكم الصورة
Luffy!
لوفي
Damn.
سحقًا
I'll handle it, Pedro!
دع هذا لي يا بيدرو
Ocean Current...
مد تيار البحر
Shoulder Throw!
أيبنزويوي
Run!
اهرب
Don't explain my powers to them...
لا تقم بشرح قدرتي لهم
That was close...
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Katakuri ate a special paramecia fruit.
كاتاكوري أكل فاكهة من نوع باراميشيا مميزة
The Mochi-Mochi Fruit.
إنها فاكهة الموتشي
Jinbe!
جينبي؟
You can escape if there's enough moisture, but try not to touch it instead.
يمكنك التخلص من قدرته بأيّ سائل ويُفضّل ألّا تلمسها بالأساس
Jinbe?
جينبي؟
I'm the one who told Luffy about Mother Carmel.
أنا الذي أخبر لوفي عن الأم كارمل
I heard all about it while I was working under you.
لقد سمعت هذه الأمور بصفتي حليفك
Those idiots! How dare they interfere...
كيف يجرؤون على التدخل؟
To come this far to take Sanji back!
كل هذه الأفعال من أجل استعادة سانجي
The wedding has been ruined...
لقد فَسد حفل الزفاف
I thought that silly Straw Hat was dead...
ظننت ذلك الساذج قبعة القش قد لقى حتفه
Don't worry, Vinsmokes.
لا حاجة للقلق يا آل فينسموك
The Charlotte family will handle this...
نحن عائلة شارلوت سنتكفل بالأمر
Lick!
بيرورين
You...
...أنت
I thought you decided not to leave my crew,
ظننتك تخليت عن فكرة مغادرة طاقمي
yet now you're sticking up for this cake wrecker?
ولكنك دافعت عن الشخص الذي أفسد الكعكة
Shall I take this as a rebellion,
أتودّ مني اعتبار ذلك خيانة صريحة منك يا جينبي؟
Yes, that's exactly what this is.
أجل، لا بأس بذلك
You have some nerve...
أنت تتحلى بالشجاعة
I wish to end our agreement...
...أريد ترك طاقمك
and join the Straw Hat Pirates!
والانضمام إلى طاقم قبعة القش
This is big news!
يا لها من أنباء صادمة
The former warlord Jinbe is joining the Straw Hat crew!
الشيتشيبوكاي السابق جينبي سينضم إلى طاقم قبعة القش
That's okay... You can do whatever you want.
لا يهم، افعل ما تشاء بعد مغادرتك
But first you have to pay the price to leave.
ولكن عليك دفع ثمن تركك لطاقمي
You don't want to live in shame, do you?
أنت رجل يأبى العيش بخزي وعار، صحيح؟
Right...
أجل
If you promise that you won't hurt anyone else,
إذا وعدتني بعدم إيذاء أحد
I'll happily give you as much of my lifespan as you can take!
سأعرض عليكِ من حياتي قدر ما تستطيعين أن تسلبي منها
Hey, what are you talking about, Jinbe?! You can't join my crew if you're dead!
مهلًا، ما الذي تقوله يا جينبي؟ لا يمكنك الانضمام لطاقمي إن مُت
I love to take people's lifespans!
كم أعشق سلب الحياة
I see... I never realized you hated me so much.
فهمت، هذا يعكس مدى كراهيتك لي
You'd rather choose death than stay somewhere you don't want to be...
أنت تفضّل الموت على البقاء في مكان لا ترغب التواجد فيه
so I won't show any mercy!
لن أشعر بالأسف عليك أبدًا
Oh... Here it is again! The Soul Pocus!
ها هي مجددًا، كلمات الروح
All right! You've got a deal!
والآن، إليك الصفقة
You fool...
أيها المغفل
Stay...
...البقاء
or...
...أو
life?
الحياة؟
Life!
الحياة
Mama...
ماما
It... can't be stopped now...
لا يمكن إيقافها الآن
Is Jinbe really going to die here...?
أيعقل أنّ هذا المكان سيشهد موت جينبي؟
Go to hell...
فلتمت
Stay or...
...البقاء أو
life!
الحياة؟
H-His soul isn't coming out of his body!
ر-روحه تأبى الخروج
You're kidding me... He's showing no fear in front of Mama!
محال، إنه غير خائف من ماما إطلاقًا
Of course not.
بالطبع
I intend to join the crew of the future pirate king...
...رجل يريد الانضمام لطاقم ملك القراصنة المستقبلي
A mere emperor does not scare me!
هيهات أن يجفل أمام محض إمبراطورة
Mama... can't take his lifespan?
ماما غير قادرة على سلب حياته؟
If you will not take my life...
...إن كنتِ لن تسلبي حياتي
then I shall return your ritual sake cup.
سأعيد كأس الساكي
As of this moment, I am leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
والآن أنا أعلن تركي لطاقم قراصنة بيغ مام
Thank you for all you've done!
شكرًا على كل شيء
I can't believe he's doing it right now...
...يفعل ذلك في منتصف الخطة
So cool... Jinbe...
ما أروعك يا جينبي
All right!
مرحى
Congratulations, Jinbe...
تهانيّ يا جينبي
but this means you're my enemy now, right?
هذا يعني أنك عدوي الآن، صحيح؟
Jinbe!
جينبي
Go to hell!
مت
Look! Over there!
انظروا هناك
H-He broke the... portrait of Mother Carmel!
لـ-لقد حطّم صورة الأم كارمل
Oh, no! This is a big deal!
مصيبة، إنه حدث يستحق التوثيق
Mama...
ماما
Yes!
مرحى
All right!
عظيم
It's broken!
تحطمت
What the hell?! I thought the fake Straw Hats were all animals!
ماذا يجري؟ ظننتُ أنّ كل أفراد طاقم قبعة القش المزيف مجرد حيوانات
Okay! Big Mom has seen the broken picture!
عظيم، لقد رأت بيغ مام الصورة المحطمة
Now, if she just shrieks...
كل ما تبقى هو أن تشرع بالصراخ الآن
What is he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
This deadly poison KX launcher is ready to fire-rero!
جاهزة للإطلاق-ريرو KX قاذفة السم الفتاك
He ripped off his face!
لقد سلخ وجهه
No! This is my real face!
كلا، هذا هو وجهي
Gross!
مقزز
I thought that you were dead!
ظننتك ميتًا
I am... But that happened a long time ago.
أجل، لقد مت منذ زمن طويل
Do you know...
...أنت
in that picture...?
أتعرف هوية صاحبتها؟
M-Mother...
ا-الأم
W-Why isn't she shrieking?
لِمَ لا تصرخ؟
Oh, no! It's just like the other day! Mama's gonna go on a rampage!
مصيبة، هذا أشبه باليوم السابق ماما فقدت صوابها
Do you have any idea who that is?
أتعلم هوية صاحبة الصورة؟
And the wedding cake!
...وفوق ذلك، كعكة الزفاف
Oh, so that's it!
هكذا هو الأمر إذًا
Mama's not thinking straight! She's gonna have a tantrum!
ماما ليست على ما يرام إنها توشك على الهلع
Kill Straw Hat and the others before that happens!
اقتلوا قبعة القش ومن معه قبل حدوث ذلك
Luffy!
...لوفي
We have to survive until Big Mom panics!
علينا البقاء على قيد الحياة حتى تصاب ماما بالهلع
Okay!
حسنًا
Straw Hat!
قبعة القش
Help!
النجدة
Stop it! Get off of me!
توقف، دعني
Are you okay, Pudding-chan ?
هل أنتِ بخير يا بودينغ-تشان؟
Let's get you somewhere safe.
لنذهب لمكان آمن
Stop, Pudding-chan !
توقفي يا بودينغ-تشان
Shut up!
اخرس
Look! This is who I truly am!
انظر إلى حقيقتي
Aren't you shocked and disappointed?!
لا بدّ أنك مصدوم وخائب الأمل
Don't worry.
...لا تقلق
You'll be dead soon!
ستموت حالًا
I've fooled many people like this!
خدعتُ أعدادًا لا تحصى بهذه الطريقة
Including yourself?!
بمن فيهم نفسك؟
You've been fooling yourself, haven't you, Pudding-chan ?
لطالما كنتِ تخدعين نفسك، أليس كذلك يا بودينغ-تشان؟
Sh... Shut up!
ا-اخرس
Move aside, Pudding!
تنحي يا بودينغ
Pudding-chan !
بودينغ-تشان
Are you okay, Pudding-chan ?
هل أنتِ بخير يا بودينغ-تشان؟
You blew it! You're useless!
أفسدتِ الأمر يا عديمة الفائدة
Big Brother Daifuku!
أخي دايفوكو
We needed you to kill the groom.
لن يبدأ شيء قبل قتلك للعريس
Let go of me!
دعني
Go, jinni!
انطلق أيها المارد
Jinni!
المارد
What's that?!
ما هذا؟
Brother Daifuku!
أخي دايفوكو
Wait! I promise I'll get it done!
تمهل، سأتولى الأمر حتمًا
You couldn't do it then... You won't do it now!
لم تتمكني من إنجاز المهمة حينها، انتهت فرصتك
Pudding-chan !
بودينغ-تشان
Jinn-uinely Enraged Cleave
طارد الشر
Collier Strike!
هجوم لحمة العنق
Stop!
توقفوا
Don't abuse my powers anymore!
كفوا عن استغلالي
Shut up! My heart is at stake!
اصمتي أيتها العجوز، استعادة قلبي مرهونة بذلك
These guys just won't stop.
كم أنتم عنيدون
What are you doing, Bege?!
ماذا تفعل يا بيجي؟
Be quiet! I'm the head of security! They'll suspect me if I do nothing!
صمتًا، أنا مسؤول الأمن سأثير الشكوك إن لم أتدخل
I got the captain!
نلتُ من قبطانهم
Alright! Kill him!
عظيم، اقتله
That might not be a bad idea.
تبدو فكرة قتلك مغرية الآن
Screw you!
كفاك عبثًا
Listen! We're in trouble.
أنصت، الوضع حرج
Why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
لِمَ لا تصرخ بيغ مام؟
I can't fight this many!
لا يمكنني مقارعة كل هؤلاء
Jinbe!
جينبي
Oven!
أوفن
You bastard!
أيها اللعين
Hey, Pedro! Don't let him land any hits on you!
يا بيدرو، لا تدعه يلمسك بضرباته
Wha... What the...?!
ماذا؟
I remember you, Pedro!
أنا أتذكرك يا بيدرو
Pekoms calls you his big brother.
أنت بمثابة الأخ الأكبر لبيكومز
You failed to steal Mama's poneglyph.
جئتَ بغية سرقة بونغليف ماما وفشلت فشلًا ذريعًا
You lost an eye and years of your lifespan as a result.
ثمّ فقدت عينًا ومدّة من حياتك بكل بؤس
Yet you've returned here, despite the limited time you have left...
...عودتك رغم قصر مدة حياتك المتبقية تعني
So you're prepared to die, right?
أنك مستعد للموت، أليس كذلك؟
I've always been prepared!
لطالما كنتُ على أهبة الاستعداد
I'll burn you to death!
سأقتلك حرقًا
It's been way longer than three seconds!
مرت الثواني الثلاث منذ فترة
What's going on?
ما الذي يجري؟
She's not shrieking at all!
إنها لا تصرخ إطلاقًا
Brook!
بروك
I'm okay. I'm alive. I mean, I'm dead...
أنا بخير، أنا حي رغم أنني ميت
I didn't know you could do that!
لم أكن أعلم أنّ بوسعك فعل هذا
Anyway, listen to me, Luffy-san !
على أي حال، انصت إليّ يا لوفي-سان
What the hell are you doing?!
ماذا تفعلون بالضبط؟
How could you do this to us!
كيف تجرؤون على ارتكاب هذه الفعلة بحقنا؟
Oh, no! Bege, get off of me!
مصيبة، ابتعد يا بيجي
Damn! This wasn't supposed to happen.
سحقًا، ما كان ينبغي بالأمور أن تسير هكذا
Tell me this is a mistake!
...ما معنى كل هذا
Big Mom!
يا بيغ مام
Lick.
بيرورين
I trusted you! Even the underworld is ruled by honor and decency!
لقد وضعتُ ثقتي فيك، حتى عالم الجريمة يحكمه الشرف
Say something!
تكلمي
Don't be pathetic, Father.
هذا ليس الوقت المناسب للفزع يا أبي
It's already too late for us.
لن ننجو بلا شك
We're trapped by this candy.
نحن مقيدون بالحلوى
And they already took all of our weapons. We don't even have our raid suits.
لقد سلبونا كل أسلحتنا وبذلات القتال
We've been totally set up. I guess we were too ambitious.
وقعنا في فخهم، يبدو أنّ طموحاتنا كانت أكبر من حجمنا
What's so funny, you fools?!
ما المضحك أيها الأوغاد؟
The one who removed all empathy from your sons was you,
...أنت المسؤول عن قسوة قلوبهم
Father.
يا أبتي
They don't even fear their own deaths...
ما عادوا يخشون الموت حتى
They're my younger brothers, but even I can't call them human.
رغم أنهم إخوتي الصغار، فأنا لا أعدهم بشرًا
Oh, boy. I've never seen such a pathetic assassination!
عجبًا، لم يسبق لي رؤية اغتيال بائس كهذا
This feels more like a cruel execution. Lick.
إنها أشبه بمذبحة-بيرورين
Don't you agree, Judge?
ألا توافقني يا جادج؟
I have... devoted my whole life...
...لقد كرّستُ كامل حياتي
my very existence...
...وكل ما لديّ
toward getting revenge on the countries in the North Blue!
من أجل الانتقام من دول الأزرق الشمالي
To restore the Empire of Germa!
واستعادة مجد إمبراطورية جيرما
Big Mom!
...بيغ مام
Say something, Big Mom!!
قولي أي شيء يا بيغ مام
Look at yourself!
يا له من منظر
What? Germa's gonna get wiped out?
ماذا؟ جيرما توشك أن تُباد؟
Oh! This is big news!
إنها أنباء صادمة
He's crying!
إنه يبكي
Tell me... it's not true!
أخبريني... أنّ هذا كذب
It's no use. Look at Mama.
لا فائدة، انظر إلى ماما
She's dazed by these shocking events.
أصابتها الأحداث الصادمة المختلفة بالارتباك
It made me a little nervous when the portrait of Mother Carmel was broken,
أصابني القلق عند تحطم صورة الأم كارمل
but the intensity of her anger has overwhelmed her grief, so we're okay.
ولكن حدة غضب ماما دفعتها لآخر حدود الجنون، لا بأس
I truly understand your burning ambition, Judge...
أنا أتفهم حقًّا طموحك الشغوف يا جادج
Lick.
بيرورين
But do you listen to what a cow has to say when you're about to eat it?
ولكن هل يكترث المرء بخوار البقرة قبل التهامها؟
Your death will nourish us, Germa 66!
لتهلكوا ولتصبح مملكتكم إرثًا لنا يا جيرما 66
Sanji's family...
عائلة سانجي
Luffy-san, listen to me!
لوفي-سان، اسمعني
Big Mom has experienced too many shocks in quick succession,
لقد مرّت بيغ مام بصدمات متتالية
so she doesn't know how to focus her anger.
وهي عاجزة عن تركيز غضبها
We should show her the broken portrait again!
لنُرِها الصورة المحطمة مرة أخرى
Okay! I'll do it if you think it's best!
فهمت، إن كان هذا قولك، سأجرّب
Hey, isn't it too late...?
مهلًا، ألم يَفُت الأوان...؟
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
That guy from earlier is coming!
ذلك الشخص الذي قابلناه سابقًا قادم
Katakuri!
كاتاكوري
All right! Carry on! That plan will work!
فلتمضِ قدمًا، الخطة ستنجح
Katakuri is looking pale!
كاتاكوري يبدو شاحبًا
That means he's seen a future where things get messy.
بمعنى آخر، لقد رأى شيئًا صادمًا في المستقبل
Go, Straw Hat!
انطلق يا قبعة القش
Okay!
مفهوم
Jinbe! Pedro!
جينبي، بيدرو
We gotta back Straw Hat up with all we've got! Follow me!
علينا دعم قبعة القش بكل ما لدينا، اتبعاني
Allied forces!
...أيتها القوات المتحالفة
All of you, get your Invisible Symphonia ready!
لتجهزوا جميعًا السيمفونيا الخفية الخاصة
– Invi... – Oh!
أجل، سدادات الأذن
Bege?
بيجي؟
What did he yell out all of a sudden?!
بماذا صرخ فجأة؟
Can you make it?!
أيمكنكم النجاح؟
Will it work in time?! Our only chance is to neutralize everyone with a gun all at once!
أنت تدرك بأنّ هذا خيارنا الوحيد لإسقاط الجميع مع أسلحتهم، أليس كذلك؟
Bege!
بيجي
Shoot Straw Hat to death now!
أطلق النار على قبعة القش حتى الموت حالًا
I refuse.
أرفض
All right! If I show this to Big Mom again, the plan's back on track, right?
عظيم، إن أريتُ هذه لبيغ مام مجددًا ستعود الأمور إلى مسارها المخطط له، أليس كذلك؟
Flambage Shot!
الركلة الملتهبة
You can see slightly ahead into the future.
قدرتك على معرفة المستقبل تقتصر على رؤيته فقط
But even if we can't see it,
...حتى إن لم نكن قادرين على رؤيته
we all have the right...
...فإنّ الحق في تغييره
to change the future!
محفوظ لنا جميعًا
S... traw... Ha... t...!
...قبعة... القش
About Three and a Half Hours Ago Bege's Hideout
قبل ثلاث ساعات ونصف مخبأ بيجي
In the Present The Wedding Venue
في الوقت الحاضر - قاعة الزفاف
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Inside the Cake
داخل الكعكة
Charlotte Daifuku Third Son of the Charlotte Family (Minister of Beans) A Lamp Man Who Ate the Puff-Puff Fruit
(الابن الثالث لعائلة شارلوت (وزير الفاصولياء شارلوت دايفوكو رجل مصباح مستخدم فاكهة دخان المصباح
Charlotte Daifuku Third Son of the Charlotte Family (Minister of Beans) A Lamp Man Who Ate the Puff-Puff Fruit
(الابن الثالث لعائلة شارلوت (وزير الفاصولياء شارلوت دايفوكو رجل مصباح مستخدم فاكهة دخان المصباح
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Charlotte Oven Fourth Son of the Charlotte Family (Minister of Browned Food) An Intense Heat Human Who Ate the Heat-Heat Fruit
الابن الرابع لعائلة شارلوت (وزير التحميص) شارلوت أوفن رجل الحرارة العالية مستخدم فاكهة السخونة
Charlotte Oven Fourth Son of the Charlotte Family (Minister of Browned Food) An Intense Heat Human Who Ate the Heat-Heat Fruit
الابن الرابع لعائلة شارلوت (وزير التحميص) شارلوت أوفن رجل الحرارة العالية مستخدم فاكهة السخونة